[
    {"problem": "카이 __  __", "answer": "스트", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "카이 __  __", "answer": "마루", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "카이 __  __", "answer": "티비", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "카이 __  __", "answer": "사르", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "도라 __  __", "answer": "에몽", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "도라 __  __", "answer": "지즙", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "도라 __  __", "answer": "지꽃", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "삼시 __  __", "answer": "세끼", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "셜록 __  __", "answer": "홈즈", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "스폰 __  __", "answer": "지밥", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "신데 __  __", "answer": "렐라", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "야인 __  __", "answer": "시대", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "레드 __  __", "answer": "벨벳", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "모모 __  __", "answer": "랜드", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "버벌 __  __", "answer": "진트", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "게르 __  __", "answer": "마늄", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "게르 __  __", "answer": "만족", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "덤프 __  __", "answer": "트럭", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "비트 __  __", "answer": "코인", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "비트 __  __", "answer": "박스", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "알레 __  __", "answer": "르기", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "알레 __  __", "answer": "그로", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "임플 __  __", "answer": "란트", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "탄수 __  __", "answer": "화물", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "루마 __  __", "answer": "니아", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "캄보 __  __", "answer": "디아", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "이탈 __  __", "answer": "리아", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "이탈 __  __", "answer": "속도", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "이탈 __  __", "answer": "시간", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "파키 __  __", "answer": "스탄", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "네덜 __  __", "answer": "란드", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "이스 __  __", "answer": "라엘", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "아프 __  __", "answer": "리카", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "이구 __  __", "answer": "아나", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "이구 __  __", "answer": "동성", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "시라 __  __", "answer": "소니", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "날다 __  __", "answer": "람쥐", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "건곤 __  __", "answer": "일척", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "건곤 __  __", "answer": "감리", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "경거 __  __", "answer": "망동", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "개과 __  __", "answer": "천선", "type": "text"},
    {"problem": "잔다 __  __", "answer": "르크", "type": "text"}
]